Contact

contact@mrkishorekumar.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ mrkishorekumar (LinkedIn) mrkishorekumar.com (Portfolio) blog.mrkishorekumar.com (Blog)

Top Skills

Python (Programming Language)
JavaScript
Machine Learning

Languages

English (Full Professional)
Tamil (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

HTML & CSS - Certification Course for Beginners

Complete Wordpress Website Developer Course

jQuery

SolidWorks Basics

Learning Python

Publications

Learn HTML5: A Beginner's Guide to HTML and Web Graphic.

Kishore Kumar M R

Mechanical Student - Python - JavaScript Coimbatore

Summary

Second year student pursuing Mechanical Engineering in Sri Shakthi Institute of Engineering and Technology, Coimbatore. I am always ready to have new experiences, meet new people and learn new things. I find the idea of creating value for people and impacting the world through my work gratifying.

As a mechanical engineer, I have been doing various projects regarding design, programing and analysis of different machines. Also, I am interested in designing the vehicles for some race events and make many designs which can be done on my own or together with other professionals.

♦ I also wrote a book called "Learn HTML5" which summarizes my experience of using HTML5 and it is a guide for college students to find opportunities, build their brand, and grow their Website.

I am very interested in Machine Learning (ML) and it's amazing to learn about its applications in various fields like crime detection, predicting diseases like cancer and Parkinson's, use of Big Data to target ads, self driving cars, creation of unique art and music. I am proficient in Python.

- ✓ I enjoy challenges that enable me to grow. I like to find application in what is taught to me and use Feynman and Pomodoro techniques to learn as quickly as possible.
- ✓ Having lived all around the country and meeting a lot of people, I'm able to adapt to any surrounding or circumstance.
- ✓ I love Graphic Designing and have made more than a 50+ Poster's and carousel decks for YouTube Thumbnail and Instagram.

Experience

YouTube
Digital Creator
January 2021 - Present (6 months)

Blogger Freelance Blogger October 2020 - Present (9 months)

Artiwiz Technologies

Wordpress Developer & Graphic Designer February 2021 - February 2021 (1 month) India

Education

Sri Shakthi Institute of Engineering and Technology
B E Mechanical Engineer, Mechanical Engineering (2019 - 2023)

National Model Coimbatore

12th, Physics, Chemistry, Mathematics, Computer Science, English and
French. (2017 - 2019)

Satchidananda Jothi Nikethan International School 10th, History, Geography, Political Science, English, Economics, Mathematics, Science, Tamil. · (2008 - 2017)